<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Movies>
    <Movie id="1">
        <Name>The Shawshank Redemption</Name>
        <Director>Frank Darabont</Director>
        <Year>1994</Year>
        <Ratings>9.3</Ratings>
        <About>Two imprisoned men bond over a number of years, finding solace and eventual redemption through acts of common decency.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="2">
        <Name>Pulp Fiction</Name>
        <Director>Quentin Tarantino</Director>
        <Year>1994</Year>
        <Ratings>8.9</Ratings>
        <About>The lives of two mob hitmen, a boxer, a gangster and his wife, and a pair of diner bandits intertwine in four tales of violence and redemption.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="3">
        <Name>Fight Club</Name>
        <Director>David Fincher</Director>
        <Year>1999</Year>
        <Ratings>8.8</Ratings>
        <About>An insomniac office worker and a devil-may-care soapmaker form an underground fight club that evolves into something much, much more.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="4">
        <Name>Forrest Gump</Name>
        <Director>Robert Zemeckis</Director>
        <Year>1994</Year>
        <Ratings>8.8</Ratings>
        <About>The presidencies of Kennedy and Johnson, the events of Vietnam, Watergate and other historical events unfold through the perspective of an Alabama man with an IQ of 75, whose only desire is to be reunited with his childhood sweetheart.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="5">
        <Name>Inception</Name>
        <Director>Christopher Nolan</Director>
        <Year>2010</Year>
        <Ratings>8.8</Ratings>
        <About>A thief who steals corporate secrets through the use of dream-sharing technology is given the inverse task of planting an idea into the mind of a C.E.O.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="6">
        <Name>The Matrix</Name>
        <Director>Wachowski Brothers</Director>
        <Year>1999</Year>
        <Ratings>8.7</Ratings>
        <About>When a beautiful stranger leads computer hacker Neo to a forbidding underworld, he discovers the shocking truth--the life he knows is the elaborate deception of an evil cyber-intelligence.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="7">
        <Name>Interstellar</Name>
        <Director>Christopher Nolan</Director>
        <Year>2014</Year>
        <Ratings>8.6</Ratings>
        <About>A team of explorers travel through a wormhole in space in an attempt to ensure humanity's survival.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="8">
        <Name>Gladiator</Name>
        <Director>Ridley Scott</Director>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Ratings>8.5</Ratings>
        <About>A former Roman General sets out to exact vengeance against the corrupt emperor who murdered his family and sent him into slavery.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="9">
        <Name>The Departed</Name>
        <Director>Martin Scorsese</Director>
        <Year>2006</Year>
        <Ratings>8.5</Ratings>
        <About>An undercover cop and a mole in the police attempt to identify each other while infiltrating an Irish gang in South Boston.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="10">
        <Name>Whiplash</Name>
        <Director>Damien Chazelle</Director>
        <Year>2014</Year>
        <Ratings>8.5</Ratings>
        <About>A promising young drummer enrolls at a cut-throat music conservatory where his dreams of greatness are mentored by an instructor who will stop at nothing to realize a student's potential.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="11">
        <Name>Avengers: Infinity War</Name>
        <Director>Anthony Russo and Joe Russo</Director>
        <Year>2018</Year>
        <Ratings>8.4</Ratings>
        <About>The Avengers and their allies must be willing to sacrifice all in an attempt to defeat the powerful Thanos before his blitz of devastation and ruin puts an end to the universe.</About>
    </Movie>
    <Movie id="12">
        <Name>Avengers: Endgame</Name>
        <Director>Anthony Russo, Joe Russo</Director>
        <Year>2019</Year>
        <Ratings>8.4</Ratings>
        <About>After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War (2018), the universe is in ruins. With the help of remaining allies, the Avengers assemble once more in order to reverse Thanos' actions and restore balance to the universe.</About>
    </Movie>
</Movies>